marriageandbeyond.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy Policy - Marriage and Beyond

## Privacy Policy for www.marriageandbeyond.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **marriageandbeyond@gmail.com**

At www.marriageandbeyond.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.marriageandbeyond.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.marriageandbeyond.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.marriageandbeyond.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, .

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.marriageandbeyond.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.marriageandbeyond.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.marriageandbeyond.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

=======================

**DISCLOSURE**

This policy is valid from the time we have launched this site in 21 December 2007

This blog is a collaborative blog written by both me and my husband. For questions about this blog, please contact  **marriageandbeyond@gmail.com**

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

This blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though we receive compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. But know that very often, we express our own personal opinions (unless otherwise stated).

This blog may contain content which might present a conflict of interest, which is but understandable with companies that have similar products and services. This content may not always be identified.
